Edwin Diamond Political Audiovisual Collection
Edwin Diamond Political Audiovisual Collection
- Tapes D0600-D0899
  - D0826 MOST - Japan U.S. - edited tape (Box 33)
  - D0827 New York Windows: Election Preview (Box 33)
  - D0828 NH Dem. Ads (Box 33)
  - D0829 Performing Arts: Jerome Robbins - That's Entertainment (Box 34)
  - D0830 Political Commercials (Box 34)
  - D0831 Puzzle Mania, or How Puzzle Weekend Changed Its Name (Box 34)
  - D0832 Riot Compilation (Box 34)
  - D0833 My Dinner with Andre (Box 34)
  - D0834 TV Politics / TV Diplomacy / End of Rockwe / Bedtime for Bonzo (Box 34)
  - D0835 Verdict: Conn. vs. Ligon (Box 34)
  - D0836 Vietnam © (Box 34)
  - D0837 Vietnam 1 & 2 / Russ - US Relations / Cambridge Debate (Box 34)
  - D0838 Vietnam 3, 4, 5 (Box 34)
  - D0839 Watergate, Moyers Essay, Hearings (Box 34)
  - D0840 Who's Teaching Our Kids? (Box 34)
  - D0841 Wooten (Box 34)
  - D0842 Word of Mouth #16 (Box 34)
  - D0843 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0844 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0845 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0846 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0847 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0848 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0849 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0850 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0851 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0852 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0853 Evening News - Producer: ABC, 3/4 - 8/85 (Box 34)
    Betacam
  - D0854 Boston - Producer: ABC - WNT - Ch. 5, 6/2 - 3/80 (Box 34)
  - D0855 Evening News - Producer: CBS, 3/14/85 (Box 34)
  - D0856 The Nightly Business Report - Producer: Ch 2, 3/4 - 8/85 (Box 34)
  - D0857 Super Tuesday / Primary Coverage, NJ, SD, CA, RI, OH, MT, WV, NM - Producer: Ch. 7/CBS, 6/3/80 (Box 34)
  - D0858 Evening News - Producer: NBC, 3/7 - 8/?? (Box 34)
  - D0859 Music Videos (Box 34)
  - D0860 Unidentified (label in another language, possibly Chinese) (Box 34)
  - D0861 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0862 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0863 WW2 Era - Ed Murrow - I can See it Now Wind Up Dog / Coming & Going / Mr. Faux Pas. - Producer: Adweek Radio Campaign, Spring 1984 (Box 34)
    1/4 inch audio cassette
  - D0864 Outlook "Outing" - Producer: BBC World Service, 4/11/90 (Box 34)
  - D0865 I Remember Truman - Producer: Chicago Symposium, 7/21/94 (Box 34)
  - D0866 I Remember Truman (3 of 3) - Producer: Chicago Symposium, 7/21/94 (Box 34)
  - D0867 Power Training: How to Win at the Media Game - Producer: Communication Concepts Inc., 1990; 3 tapes (Box 34)
  - D0868 Inner Healing Ruth Carter Stapleton - Producer: Creative Resources / Word Inc., 1976; 2 tapes in case (Box 34)
  - D0869 What I meant Was...: Making Media Work for You - Producer: Kathleen Hessert & Associates Interviews, 1987; 3 tapes (Box 34)
  - D0870 AIDS: The Fears and Facts - Producer: NBC Radio Network (Box 34)
  - D0871 AIDS. The Killer Epidemic Continues - Producer: NBC Radio Network (Box 34)
  - D0872 Spencer 3 - Producer: Paul E. Schindler Jr. (Box 34)
  - D0873 Spencer 1 & 2 - Producer: Paul E. Schindler Jr. (Box 34)
  - D0874 Jingle Demo: Carvel, Nerf, NY Air, M&M's, Huggies - Producer: Sharon Weintraub (Box 34)
  - D0875 Jack Benporad Sermon 1981 - Producer: Tony Schwartz (Box 34)
  - D0876 ADM. Noel Gayler On Nuclear Cuts - Dolby B - Producer: Tony Schwartz, 1983 (Box 34)
  - D0877 Interview w/ Tony Schwartz - Producer: Tony Schwartz, 7/6/83 (Box 34)
  - D0878 Pope John Paul II Radio Spot - Producer: Tony Schwartz (Box 34)
  - D0879 West Virginia Democratic Committee License Plates - Producer: Tony Schwartz (Box 34)
  - D0880 Carter Radio Spots 1976 Campaign, 2/5/77 (Box 34)
  - D0881 Garth, Empty Case no tape (Box 34)
  - D0882 Garth Cx NYC, 4/20/83 (Box 34)
  - D0883 Rossen [?] Reeves - NYC, 6/27/83 (Box 34)
  - D0884 Tony Schwartz Session to Furnegan[?] Unitel, 7/19/83 (Box 34)
  - D0885 Ailes [?] (side 3 of 3), 8/15/83 (Box 34)
  - D0886 Dresner NYC, 8/15/83 (Box 34)
  - D0887 Roger Ailes [?] (Sides 1 & 2 of 3), 8/15/83 (Box 34)
  - D0888 Garth II Show & Tell, 8/2/83 (Box 34)
  - D0889 Dictation ED/DC (Box 34)
  - D0890 Edwin Diamond - Spectrum 4 shows (Box 34)
  - D0891 Jimmy Carter on "What's My Line" (Box 34)
  - D0892 Reagan Ads Jackson, Harris, Shriver (Box 34)
  - D0893 unlabeled (Box 34)
  - D0894 High or Low - Substance and Nonsense in the Ford/Carter Debates - Producer: 17.24 Aaron Endelman (Box 35)
    1/2 inch videotape: EIAJ Type 1
  - D0895 Violence on Television: Scenes from Kojak and the Godfather - Producer: 17.24 Gwen Freeman (Box 35)
  - D0896 The Role of Visuals in TV News - Producer: 17.24 Pete Lemme, Karen Fabricios, Mark Vershel (Box 35)
  - D0897 Nixon's Trial (early Speeches, Excerpts from Watergate, Resignation) - Producer: 17.27 Jay Yabloon, Spring 1975 (Box 35)
  - D0898 Ted Kennedy at Harbor Opening Ceremonies / Boston / Nixon After Watergate / Julian Bond on AM America - Producer: 3 Local Boston Stations, 7/8/75 - 8/8/75 - 7/15/75 (Box 35)
  - D0899 NH NBC local - ABC national / Shriver on News Conference - Producer: ABC, 2/29/?? (Box 35)
- Tapes D0900-D1199
  - D0900 Frank Church - Producer: ABC, 12/23/??, 3/2/?? (Box 35)
  - D0901 Ch. 5 News & Special / NH Primary ABC - Producer: ABC (Box 35)
  - D0902 Good Morning Loeb & Carter / 6PM News Ch. 5 - Jackson AD / ABC News - Producer: ABC (Box 35)
  - D0903 Udall - Face the Nation / Jackson, Shapp - Issues and Answers / ABC News - Producer: ABC (Box 35)
  - D0904 Today / NBC News / ABC News / Channel 5 Election Special - Producer: ABC (Box 35)
  - D0905 Jackson, Carter, Udall, Wallace, Church - Issues and Answers - Producer: ABC (Box 35)
  - D0906 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 10/11 - 12/?? (Box 35)
  - D0907 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 10/12 - 18/?? (Box 35)
  - D0908 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 10/16 - 17/?? (Box 35)
  - D0909 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 10/20/?? (Box 35)
  - D0910 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 10/2 - 10/72 (Box 35)
  - D0911 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 10/23 - 25/?? (Box 35)
  - D0912 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 10/5 - 6/?? (Box 36)
  - D0913 News / Today - Illinois - Producer: ABC, 3/3 - 16/?? (Box 36)
  - D0914 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 9/26 - 27/??; 9/26 bad (Box 36)
  - D0915 [no title] - Producer: ABC/NBC, 9/18/??, 10/9/?? (Box 36)
  - D0916 Evening News - Producer: ABC, 10/27/72 (Box 36)
  - D0917 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 9/25/72 - 10/3/72 (Box 36)
  - D0918 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 9/26 - 29/72 (Box 36)
  - D0919 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 10/27 - 30/72 (Box 36)
  - D0920 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 10/31 - 11/1/72; no sound? (Box 36)
  - D0921 John Appel - Producer: ABC, 11/3/72 (Box 36)
  - D0922 [no title] - Producer: ABC, 11/6/72 (Box 36)
  - D0923 Watergate Hearings & Election Coverage - Producer: ABC, 5/22/73 (Box 36)
  - D0924 New York, Wisconsin - Good Morning America - Producer: ABC, 4/6 - 7/76 (Box 36)
  - D0925 Watergate Hearings / '72 Election Coverage - Producer: ABC Nat'l / Local Channel 5, 5/22/73 (Box 36)
  - D0926 Ford Press Conference / Nelson Rockefeller - Meet the Press / Barry Goldwater - Issues and Answers - Producer: ABC/NBC, 6/9/75; 6/15/75 (Box 36)
  - D0927 Democratic National Telethon, Frank Church, John Glenn / Democ. Nat'l Chrm. Rodino, Kennedy, Humphrey / HHH - Issues and Answers - Producer: ABC, 7/26/75; 1/25/76 (Box 37)
  - D0928 Anti Politics - Tricia Crane Project / Scoop Jackson Good Morning Show / NBC - Foreign Policy J. Ford / ABC Wide World Spec. - Producer: ABC/NBC, 12/16/75; 1/5/76 (Box 37)
  - D0929 NH / Anchor Desk / Reasoner - Producer: ABC/WMUR - TV, 2/24/76 (Box 37)
  - D0930 Issues and Answers - Brown, Carter, Wallace, Church, Udall - Producer: ABC, 6/6/76 (Box 37)
  - D0931 Calif. Ohio, NJ / Meet the Press: Hamilton, Jordan - Producer: ABC/NBC, 6/8-20/76 (Box 37)
  - D0932 Election Night Coverage - Producer: ABC/NBC, 11/2/76 (Box 37)
  - D0933 Election Night Coverage - Producer: ABC, NBC, WCVB, WBZ, WNAC, 11/2/76 (Box 37)
  - D0934 CBS/NBC/ABC - Producer: ABC/CBS/NBC (Box 37)
  - D0935 World News - Producer: ABC, 4/9/79 (Box 37)
  - D0936 News Comparison ABC, NBC, CBS - Producer: ABC/NBC/CBS, 12/15/78 (Box 37)
  - D0937 Wallace - Face the Nation / Udall Issues and Answers - Producer: CBS (Box 37)
  - D0938 Face the Nation - Jackson / MTP (Meet the Press?) - Udall - Producer: CBS, 4/4/?? (Box 37)
  - D0939 Brown - Face the Nation - Producer: CBS, 5/9/?? (Box 37)
  - D0940 [no title] - Producer: CBS, 10/20/?? (Box 37)
  - D0941 NH - TV / Mt - MATV - Producer: CBS, 2/23 - 25/?? (Box 37)
  - D0942 Morning News Florida / Jackson MTP (Meet the Press?) - Producer: CBS, 3/10 - 14/?? (Box 37)
  - D0943 Election Special / MASS Primary / Today - Producer: CBS, 3/2 - 15/2? (Box 37)
  - D0944 NC Primary / Wallace - Meet the Press - Producer: CBS, 3/23 - 28/?? (Box 37)
  - D0945 News / Illinois, CBS - Producer: CBS, 3/3/?? (Box 37)
  - D0946 [no title] - Producer: CBS/ABC, 10/11 - 13/?? (Box 37)
  - D0947 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/12/2? (Box 38)
  - D0948 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/16/?? (Box 38)
  - D0949 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/17/?? (Box 38)
  - D0950 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/18/?? (Box 38)
  - D0951 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/19/?? (Box 38)
  - D0952 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/23/2? (Box 38)
  - D0953 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/24/2? (Box 38)
  - D0954 Schindler - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/31/?? (Box 38)
  - D0955 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/4/?? (Box 38)
  - D0956 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/5/?? (Box 38)
  - D0957 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/6/?? (Box 38)
  - D0958 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 9/14/?? (Box 38)
  - D0959 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 9/21/?? (Box 38)
  - D0960 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 9/22/?? (Box 38)
  - D0961 Penn. Primary/Dem. Conv. - Producer: CBS/WGBH - News, 4/27/?? (Box 39)
  - D0962 [no title], 9/15/72 (Box 39)
  - D0963 Evening News - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/20/72 (Box 39)
  - D0964 Evening News - Producer: CBS/NBC, 9/28/72 (Box 39)
  - D0965 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/26/72 (Box 39)
  - D0966 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/27/72 (Box 39)
  - D0967 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/30/72 (Box 39)
  - D0968 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/31/72 (Box 39)
  - D0969 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 11/1/72 (Box 39)
  - D0970 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 11/2/72 (Box 39)
  - D0971 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 11/3/72; Tape Damage (Box 39)
  - D0972 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 11/6/72 (Box 39)
  - D0973 [no title] - Producer: CBS/NBC, 10/25/73 (Box 39)
  - D0974 Nixon Checkers Speech 1952 /'72 Election Night Coverage, - Producer: CBS - Ch. 4 Local, 11/1/73 (Box 39)
  - D0975 H.R. Haldeman Interview with Mike Wallace 1 of 2 - Producer: CBS, 3/23/75 (Box 39)
  - D0976 H.R. Haldeman Interview with Mike Wallace 2 of 2 - Producer: CBS, 3/30/75 (Box 39)
  - D0977 New York, Wisconsin / Morning News - Producer: CBS, 4/6 - 7/76 (Box 39)
  - D0978 Ronald Reagan - Face the Nation / Morris Udall - Face the Nation / Reuben Askew - Meet the Press - - Producer: CBS, 6/1/75; 6/8/75,; 6/8/75 (Box 40)
  - D0979 Face the Nation - John Connally / Good Morning Sargent Shriver / Good Morning Wallace - Producer: CBS, 10/12/75; 10/20/75,; 1/12/76 (Box 40)
  - D0980 Bo Calloway - Face the Nation / Ronald Reagan - 60 Min. / George Wallace - Face the Nation - Producer: CBS, 12/7 - 14/75; 1/11/76 (Box 40)
  - D0981 Face the Nation / Meet the Press - Connally - Producer: CBS/NBC, 6/6 - 13/76 (Box 40)
  - D0982 Calif. Ohio, New Jersey - Producer: CBS, 6/8/76 (Box 40)
  - D0983 AM / Good Morning America - Producer: CBS/ABC, 6/9/76 (Box 40)
  - D0984 Pre - Election Special - Producer: CBS, 10/31/76 (Box 40)
  - D0985 Election Night Coverage - Producer: CBS, 11/2/76 (Box 40)
  - D0986 Election Night Coverage - Producer: CBS, 11/2/76 (Box 40)
  - D0987 Presidential Primary Coverage - Michigan & Oregon - Producer: CBS, 5/20/80 (Box 40)
  - D0988 Saturday News - Melinda Stewart - Producer: CBS, Bad Tape? (Box 40)
  - D0989 Impact: The Credibility of Television News - Kolowich - Producer: Ch. 4, 1973 (Box 40)
  - D0990 Desegregation Coverage - News, Interviews, Features - Producer: Ch. 4, 5 - Local, 1/22/76 (Box 40)
  - D0991 Watergate Hearings - Producer: Ch. 44, 5/17/73 (Box 40)
  - D0992 Desegregation Coverage - News/Interviews/Features - Producer: Channel 7 local (Box 40)
  - D0993 Mackin, Wheat Deal, Watergate, Pre - election - Producer: Highlights (Box 40)
  - D0994 Desegregation Coverage Winter 1976 - Producer: Local Channels (Box 40)
  - D0995 Curtis Wilkie Globe - Producer: MITV, 1976 (Box 40)
  - D0996 Pro - Busing - Interview an Busing Coverage - Producer: NAACP, 3/26/76 (Box 40)
  - D0997 End of Wallace - Face the Nation - Meet the Press - Producer: NBC, 1/11/?? (Box 40)
  - D0998 Ch. 4 News & Special /NBC NH Primary - Producer: NBC, 2/24/?? (Box 40)
  - D0999 Ronald Reagan - Meet the Press / Jerry Brown - 60 Minutes - Producer: NBC, 3/7/?? (Box 41)
  - D1000 HHH - Meet the Press / Nelson Rockefeller - Issues and Answers - Producer: NBC, 11/2/?? (Box 41)
  - D1001 Face the Nation - Carter / Meet the Press - Moudal - Producer: NBC, 11/30/?? (Box 41)
  - D1002 North Carolina Primary Special / Frank Church - Today - Producer: NBC, 3/23 - 30/?? (Box 41)
  - D1003 News / Illinois, NBC - Producer: NBC, 3/3 - 16/?? (Box 41)
  - D1004 Today - Alabama, Georgia, Indiana, Washington - Producer: NBC, 5/5/?? (Box 41)
  - D1005 Harris ? News / Ads - Ford, Udall, McCormack, Shriver, Harris / Wallace News - Producer: NBC/CBS, 2/29/??, 3/1/?? (Box 41)
  - D1006 Evening News - Producer: NBC, 10/20/74 (Box 41)
  - D1007 Wallace - Meet the Press - Producer: NBC, 11/16/75 (Box 41)
  - D1008 NH Election Central - Carter Rally - Producer: NBC, 2/22/76 (Box 41)
  - D1009 NH, Rehearsal, Wayfarer [?] - Producer: NBC, 2/22/76 (Box 41)
  - D1010 Today - 6 Primaries - Producer: NBC?, 5/6/76 (Box 41)
  - D1011 Today - Producer: NBC?, 6/7 - 8/76 (Box 41)
  - D1012 Calif. Ohio, NJ - Producer: NBC, 6/8/76 (Box 41)
  - D1013 Today - Producer: NBC, 6/9/76 (Box 41)
  - D1014 News - Producer: NBC, 10/7/76 (Box 41)
  - D1015 Meet the Press - Producer: NBC, 11/18/76 (Box 41)
  - D1016 Penn. Primary - Producer: NBC/ABC (Box 41)
  - D1017 NYC Local News 6 - 7PM - Producer: Newscenter 4, 11/18/75 (Box 42)
  - D1018 Carter Interview with Bill Moyers - Producer: PBS, 11/13/78 (Box 42)
  - D1019 U.S.A. Politics Candidate Forum - Producer: PBS, 2/23/?? (Box 42)
  - D1020 Candidates Forum Economy Tape II - Producer: PBS, 2/23/?? (Box 42)
  - D1021 Candidates Forum Economy Tape III - Producer: PBS, 2/23/?? (Box 42)
  - D1022 Inside Look at Various Aspects of the January 1976 Super bowl - Producer: PBS (Box 42)
  - D1023 Funniest Person in America - Producer: Showtime * Entertainment, 6/9/76 (Box 42)
  - D1024 Japanese Programs I - Producer: Trudi Berlin (Box 42)
  - D1025 Arsenic and Old Lace - Producer: Viking Theatre Productions (Box 42)
  - D1026 Southie WCVB Interview, Charleston - Interviews - Coverage of Busing Coverage - Producer: WCVB/PBS (Box 42)
  - D1027 6PM News - Producer: WCVB TV5, 2/3/77 (Box 42)
  - D1028 USA: People & Politics / Presidential Forum - Shapp, Jackson, Carter - Producer: WGBH, 3/1/?? (Box 42)
  - D1029 L. Dyatt - Producer: WNAC, 4/1/76 (Box 42)
  - D1030 Sheila Banks & Joyce Jefferson - Coverage of Busing Coverage - Producer: WNAC (Box 42)
  - D1031 Frank Church - Meet the Press / Birch Bayh - Issues and Answers / Ted Kennedy - Impact / Job Watch / Ronald Reagan - Today, 8/17 - 29/?? (Box 42)
  - D1032 Bo Calloway Today, 11/22/?? (Box 42)
  - D1033 Speak, 2/15/?? (Box 42)
  - D1034 Good Morning News / Ch. 4 News & Special, 2/24/?? (Box 42)
  - D1035 Today in NH, 2/24/?? (Box 42)
  - D1036 Today, 2/25/?? (Box 42)
  - D1037 Today - Illinois, 3/17/?? (Box 42)
  - D1038 Candidate Forum - The Cities - New York Tape II, 3/29/?? (Box 43)
  - D1039 Candidate Forum - New York Tape I, 3/29/?? (Box 43)
  - D1040 Today, 3/3/?? (Box 43)
  - D1041 Ronald Reagan - 1/2 speech to nation, 3/31/?? (Box 43)
  - D1042 Today New York, Wisconsin Primary, 4/7/?? (Box 43)
  - D1043 Presidential Forum - Chicago - Defense, Detente & Trade - Udall & Church, 5/3/?? (Box 43)
  - D1044 Today Florida, 3/9/?? (Box 43)
  - D1045 Kevin White Campaign For Governor v. Sargent, 1970 (Box 43)
  - D1046 Marty Linsky TV Commercials (US Congress) Fall, 1972 (Box 43)
  - D1047 Watergate Hearings, 5/18/72 (Box 43A)
  - D1048 Watergate Hearings, 5/17/73 (Box 43A)
  - D1049 Nixon and the Press - APME Convention, 11/17/73 (Box 43A)
  - D1050 #1 7:30PM Wednesday, 7/24/74 (Box 43A)
  - D1051 #2 8:32PM Wednesday, 7/24/74 (Box 43A)
  - D1052 #3 10:05PM Wednesday, 7/24/74 (Box 43A)
  - D1053 #4 10:32AM Thursday, 7/25/74 (Box 43A)
  - D1054 #5 11:36AM Thursday, 7/25/74 (Box 43A)
  - D1055 #6 2:16PM Thursday - Opening Remarks, 7/25/74 (Box 43A)
  - D1056 After Bomb Recess, 7/25/74 (Box 43A)
  - D1057 #8 5:14PM Thursday, 7/25/74 (Box 43A)
  - D1058 #9 9:16PM Thursday, 7/25/74 (Box 43A)
  - D1059 #10 10:22PM Thursday / 11:00AM Friday, 7/25 - 26/74 (Box 43A)
  - D1060 #11 12:10 noon Friday, 7/26/74 (Box 43A)
  - D1061 #12 3:30PM Friday, 7/26/74 (Box 43A)
  - D1062 #13 4:20PM Friday, 7/26/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1063 #14 5:25PM Friday, 7/26/74? (Box 43B)
  - D1064 #15 9:05PM Friday, 7/26/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1065 #16 10:10PM Friday, 7/26/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1066 #17 10:43PM Friday, 7/26/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1067 #18 11:18PM Friday - 12:27AM Saturday, 7/26 - 27/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1068 #19 1:14PM Saturday, 7/27/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1069 #20 2:20PM Saturday, 7/27/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1070 #21 5:28PM Saturday, 7/27/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1071 #22 6:44PM Saturday, 7/27/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1072 #23 11:48AM Monday, 7/29/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1073 #24 12:54 Monday, 7/29/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1074 #25 4:12PM Monday, 7/29/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1075 #26 7:40PM Monday, 7/29/74 (Box 43B)
  - D1076 #27 8:44PM Monday, 7/29/74 (Box 43)
  - D1077 #28 9:49PM Monday, 7/29/74 (Box 43)
  - D1078 #29 10:52PM Monday, 7/29/74 (Box 43)
  - D1079 #30 11:30AM Tuesday, 7/30/74 (Box 43)
  - D1080 #31 12:35PM Tuesday, 7/30/74 (Box 43)
  - D1081 #32 4:54PM Tuesday, 7/30/74 (Box 43)
  - D1082 #33 5:57PM Tuesday, 7/30/74 (Box 43)
  - D1083 #34 Tuesday, 7/30/74 (Box 44)
  - D1084 #35 10:06PM Tuesday, 7/30/74 (Box 44)
  - D1085 Nixon Resignation, 8/8/74 (Box 44)
  - D1086 Nixon Highlights, 1974 summer (Box 44)
  - D1087 Ford - Hungate Subcommittee / Post Watergate Inquiry, 11/17/74 (Box 44)
  - D1088 Ford - Hungate Subcommittee (Post Watergate Inquiry) Part II, 11/17/74 (Box 44)
  - D1089 Desegregation Coverage: interview w/ injured cop, East Campus Interviews, Transparent Horizons, 12/17/75 (Box 44)
  - D1090 Ford Press Conference, 3/6/75 (Box 44)
  - D1091 Ford Press Conference (Vietnam Assistance), 4/3/75 (Box 44)
  - D1092 Ford 'State of the World' Address, 4/10/75 (Box 44)
  - D1093 Ford with Walter Cronkite: A Conversation with the President, 4/21/75 (Box 44)
  - D1094 Ford Press Conference, 6/25/75 (Box 44)
  - D1095 Children's TV (Commercials), Fall 1975 (Box 44)
  - D1096 Robert Stafford - U.S. Senate Campaign (Vermont), Fall 1975 (Box 44)
  - D1097 Gov. Edmund Brown / AM America / Kaplone on Candidates / Pres. Ford on Tax Cuts, 10/5/75; 10/6/75,; 11/6/75 (Box 44)
  - D1098 Ford Press Conference, 11/3/75 (Box 44)
  - D1099 News Show Formats: 60 Minutes 'Tabloid TV' Tom Elik on Anchormen - Ch. 5 on Happy Talk - Walter Cronkite on Convention Coverage, 11/18/75 (Box 44)
  - D1100 Desegregation Coverage, 12/15 - 19/75; 1/6 - 9/76 (Box 45)
  - D1101 Ford State of the Union Address, 1/19/76 (Box 45)
  - D1102 Ford State of the Union Address - Part I, 11/19/76 (Box 45)
  - D1103 Muskie State of the Union Reply - Part I, 1/19/76 (Box 45)
  - D1104 Muskie State of the Union Reply - Part II, 1/21/76 (Box 45)
  - D1105 Omaha News, 11/22/76 (Box 45)
  - D1106 Jerry Brown 1/2 hour Spot, 1/26/80 (Box 45)
  - D1107 Charlestown High School, 1/30/76 (Box 45)
  - D1108 Carter News Conference - Udall Spots - Carter Ad - Carter, Jackson, McCormick, Shriver - Goldwater, Good Morning American - Ford, Harris, Shriver, 2/2/76 (Box 45)
  - D1109 First 4 News / Ads - Reagan, Udall, Carter, Harris / Bayh News Conference / Strauss on the Today Show / Ads Shriver, 2/2/76 (Box 45)
  - D1110 HN - Gibson, Margolis, Nordheimer, 2/5/76 (Box 45)
  - D1111 Ford Dinner - Nashua, 2/7/76 (Box 45)
  - D1112 New Hampshire #1 (Box 45)
  - D1113 New Hampshire #3 (Box 45)
  - D1114 New Hampshire #4 (Box 45)
  - D1115 New Hampshire #5 (Box 45)
  - D1116 New Hampshire #9 (Box 45)
  - D1117 New Hampshire #10 (Box 45)
  - D1118 New Hampshire #14 (Box 45)
  - D1119 New Hampshire #15 (Box 45)
  - D1120 New Hampshire #16 (Box 45)
  - D1121 New Hampshire #21 - Broder Interview (Box 45)
  - D1122 New Hampshire #22 (Box 45)
  - D1123 New Hampshire #23 (Box 45)
  - D1124 New Hampshire #24 (Box 45)
  - D1125 New Hampshire #25 (Box 45)
  - D1126 New Hampshire #27 (Box 45)
  - D1127 New Hampshire #29 Ford, 2/7/76 (Box 45)
  - D1128 New Hampshire #30 Ford, 2/7/76 (Box 45)
  - D1129 New Hampshire #31 Reagan / High School Rally, 2/4/76 (Box 45)
  - D1130 New Hampshire #32 - N. Sutton H.S. Rally, 2/4/76 (Box 45)
  - D1131 New Hampshire #33 - Jon Nordheimer, 2/5/76 (Box 45)
  - D1132 New Hampshire #34 - Reagan Bus (Amy Interview), 2/5/76 (Box 46)
  - D1133 New Hampshire #36 - Reagan, 2/5/76 (Box 46)
  - D1134 New Hampshire #37 - Reagan, Dartmouth, K. Rink, 2/5/76 (Box 46)
  - D1135 New Hampshire #38 - Reagan, 2/5/76 (Box 46)
  - D1136 New Hampshire #39 - Ford, 2/5/76 (Box 46)
  - D1137 New Hampshire #40 - Reagan, Dartmouth, 2/5/76 (Box 46)
  - D1138 New Hampshire #41 - Reagan (Dartmouth - K. Rink), 2/5/76 (Box 46)
  - D1139 New Hampshire #42 - Ford Bus (Reeves Int.), 2/7/76 (Box 46)
  - D1140 New Hampshire #44, 2/7/76 (Box 46)
  - D1141 New Hampshire #45 Ford, Nessen/Reeves, 2/7/76 (Box 46)
  - D1142 New Hampshire #46 - Ford, 2/7/76 (Box 46)
  - D1143 New Hampshire #47 - Ford, 2/8/76 (Box 46)
  - D1144 New Hampshire #48 - Reagan / Hampton Beach, 2/10/76 (Box 46)
  - D1145 New Hampshire #49 - Ford, 2/8/76 (Box 46)
  - D1146 New Hampshire #50 - Ford, 2/8/76 (Box 46)
  - D1147 New Hampshire #52 - Reagan Bus, UNH Rally, 2/10/76 (Box 46)
  - D1148 New Hampshire #54 - Harris/Reagan, 2/12/76 (Box 46)
  - D1149 New Hampshire #55 - Reagan, 2/12/76 (Box 46)
  - D1150 New Hampshire #56 - Reagan, 2/12/76 (Box 46)
  - D1151 New Hampshire #58 (Loeb), 2/11/76 (Box 46)
  - D1152 New Hampshire #73 - Mrs. Carter, RR Rally (Box 46)
  - D1153 Political Ads '76 Campaign - Wallace, Jackson, Carter, McCormack, Udall / Pat Paulson on Tonight Show / Ford News Conference on CIA, 2/16 - 17/76 (Box 46)
  - D1154 NH Dick Stout, 2/17/76 (Box 46)
  - D1155 Wrap up Interview with Stout, 2/17/76 (Box 46)
  - D1156 NH Carter in Berlin, 2/18/76 (Box 46)
  - D1157 NH - Carter in Berlin Radio Station Interview, 2/18/76 (Box 46)
  - D1158 NH - Reagan Press Conference Manchester, 2/19/76 (Box 46)
  - D1159 NH Reagan Press Conference / Margolis Interview, 2/19/76 (Box 46)
  - D1160 [no title] (Box 46)
  - D1161 NH Reagan Rewind, 2/20/76 (Box 46)
  - D1162 NH Ford Visit, 2/20/76 (Box 46)
  - D1163 NH Ford Trip, 2/20/76 (Box 46)
  - D1164 SUB [?] Special. - Cond's [?] Speak, 2/21/76 (Box 46)
  - D1165 NH - Harris - Energy Press Conference / Caravan / Harris at the 'Mystery Caves', 2/21/76 (Box 46)
  - D1166 NH - Reagan Rally, 2/21/76 (Box 46)
  - D1167 NH John Years, 12/22/76 (Box 46)
  - D1168 NH Cliff Robertson, Manchester Scenes, Poll Watchers, 2/24/76 (Box 46)
  - D1169 NH John Apple, 2/25/76 (Box 46)
  - D1170 Maggie O'Keefe Anti Busing Advocate, 3/18/76 (Box 46)
  - D1171 Interview - Newspaper Reporter, 3/18/76 (Box 46)
  - D1172 Interviews - Jane Margulis, Viola Napier - Pro - Busing, 3/27/76 (Box 46)
  - D1173 Advertisements, Spring 1976 (Box 46)
  - D1174 Carter Commercials, 10/15 - 20/76 (Box 47)
  - D1175 1976 MA Senatorial Debate/Behind the Scenes / CBS '76 Election Night Coverage, 10/30/76 (Box 47)
  - D1176 Barry Goldwater - Issues and Answers / Carter on Energy, 11/8/77 (Box 47)